advantagewave.com 2010-01-02

# AdvantageWave

| 

Policy  
PRIVACY POLICY

**Collection and Use**  
We collect voluntary demographic information from users directly and through partners, including, but not limited to, user name, first and last name, e-mail address, street address, gender, occupation, and interests. We also collect information on the pages users access or visit, and other information volunteered by users, such as survey information. Additionally, for each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes IP Addresses.

We also may use cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for such purposes including to ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads and to customize newsletter and Web page content based on visitors' browser type.

**Links**  
This website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. When leaving our website, be sure to read the privacy statements of each website that collects personally identifiable information. Our privacy statement applies solely to information collected on our websites.

**Security**  
We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of members' information. We use industry standard procedures and processes to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewalls, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data.

Unfortunately, when you submit information about yourself to over the Internet the information may travel over many systems that are not under our control. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate and typical physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Unsolicited Email**  
We are committed to protecting the integrity of our web site. We encourage all members to promote our service with the highest standards of Internet etiquette and business ethics. We strictly prohibit the sending of Unsolicited Email or electronic messages of any kind to unknown individuals In addition, a member may not make any false or deceptive misrepresentations through Unsolicited Email or other advertising methods with respect to any and all compensation or products received from us or with respect to compensation or products that potential members are likely to receive.

**Privacy for Children and Minors**  
Protecting the privacy of children is important to us We will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 18 but at least 13 years of age, you may use our Websites only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by our Privacy Policy. We have designed this policy in order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from members known to be under 18, and no part of our website is designed to attract anyone under 18. It is important to remember that we cannot always determine that a member is a child under the age of 18. Members under the age of 18 must have written parental consent to release their name, email address, or other personal information. 

**Information From Third Parties**  
We may collect your information when you provide it to a third party, and we subsequently purchase, license or lawfully acquire the information from that party. The information that we collect may include your name, address, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers, birth date, gender, salary range, education, marital status, occupation, employment status, person and online interests, and other information that you may have provided to the third party. When receiving data from outside sources, we seek assurances that the party has the right to transfer the information to us, that the data was not improperly obtained, and that we have the right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose information is provided to us. 

**Practices of Third Parties**  
We cannot control, and are not responsible, for any third party’s use of cookies, web beacons or other technology to collect information about an individual. Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and  
other companies who place advertisements on Websites, email messages and on the Internet may use this or other technology to collect information about you.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is information that a website transfers to your computer for record-keeping purposes. Cookies are typically used to save a user's password so that the user does not have to re-enter their password each time they visit the same website. In addition, cookies can make the Internet more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular website. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and most websites use them to provide useful features for their members. Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can set your Internet browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a website if you do.

**IP Address**  
An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. All computer identification on the Internet is conducted with IP addresses, which allow computers and servers to recognize and communicate with each other. Your IP address does not contain your name but does provide additional demographic information.

We release IP addresses to advertisers or third parties. We use your IP address to help diagnose or detect problems with our server, for security reasons, to conduct system administration and site analysis, and to administer our website. Any demographic information collected from your IP address is added to you information and stored in our database for use by us or third parties.

**Unsubscribe**  
If you unsubscribe, you are no longer eligible to receive your products and you will not receive free email offers or information about new promotions, contests or services. If you wish to cancel your subscription, simply go to the home page and unsubscribe. You may also write to us and your request will be honored within 10 days.

**Notification of Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
The Privacy Policy may be updated to increase our members' privacy protection or to improve our information practices. If there are changes made in the future, the changes will not affect information already collected. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be available on this page for members to review.

This Privacy Policy is subject to change without notice. Please review this Privacy Policy on this website frequently to look for changes. Your continued membership will signify your unconditional acceptance to the modified terms.

|
